#### NAME: OLAOBA DEBORAH GBEMISOLA

No 20, Abimbola Street Agbowo Ui, Ibadan, Oyo State.

E-mail: olaobadeborahg@gmail.com

Mobile: +2347030204082

# **CAREER VISION**

 A self-oriented, disciplined and confident young lady with excellent interpersonal skills and ability to work with little supervision. Keen to find a challenging position within an ambitious employer where I will be able to continue to increase my work experience and develop my abilities.

#### PERSONAL DATA

Gender: Female

Date of Birth: July 30th, 1996

Marital Status: Single Nationality: Nigerian

State of Origin/LGA: Oyo/ Akinyele Local Government

### **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION**

## B.A Philosophy, April 2019

University of Ibadan, Ibadan, Nigeria

## PROFESSIONAL TRAINING AND CERTIFICATION

Certificate Awarding body Year

Human Resources Management Professional- International Institute of Project and (HRMP) Safety Management (IIPSM) - 2019

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE AND ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

Organization: Ekiti State University (EKSU), Ekiti State, Nigeria

Date: July 2019 – May 2020

Position: Administrator / Corp Member

### **Job Description**

- Administrative Worker
- Typist

Organization: Future Bright Model School, Elekuru, Ibadan, Nigeria

Date: June 2013 - January 2015
Position: Teacher and Administrator

## Job Description

- Training of young minds to become the best in life
- Handling of financial, administrative and logistic details
- Clientele relations

# TECHNICAL AND PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office, SPSS
Health, Safety and Environmental skills
Human Resources Managerial skills
Bag and Shoe Making Skills
Corel Draw Skills
Business and Marketing Skills

# SPECIAL ACHIEVEMENT

- ➤ Positive Recognition and Award from National Youth Service Corp (NYSC)
- ➤ Received very good to excellent appraisals and recommendations.

# **LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCES**

a.	Winners Corpers Fellowship, Ekiti State (Music Director)	2019
- 2020		
b.	Ekiti State University Corpers Fellowship, EKSU (Music Director)	2019
- 2020		
C.	Christian Association of Philosophy Student (CAPS) (Vice President)	2015
<b>- 2016</b>		
d.	National Association of Philosophy Press, UI (Treasurer)	2014
<b>- 2015</b>		
e.	Faculty of Art Christian Association, UI (Music Director & Treasurer) 2013	- 2014

### REFEREES

**AVAILABLE ON REQUEST**